(Howard:)I'm thinking about
getting my doctorate,
(Howard:)and he wants to teach-- why not?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Howard.
(Sheldon:)I appreciate
the gesture,
(Sheldon:)but this is
a graduate-level physics class.
(Sheldon:)I don't think you'd understand
(Sheldon:)a single thing
I was talking about.
Ask why not again;
I've got an answer.
(Howard:)Sheldon, I'm more than smart
enough to take your class.
(chuckles):
No.
(Howard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)How would you determine
the ground state
(Sheldon:)of a quantum system
with no exact solution?
(Howard:)I would guess a wave-function
and then vary its parameters
(Howard:)until I found
the lowest energy solution.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)Do you know how to integrate
X squared times E
(Sheldon:)to the minus X,
without looking it up?
(Howard:)I'd use Feynman's trick--
(Howard:)differentiate
under the integral sign.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Um...
(Sheldon:)What is the correct
interpretation